https://www.aiba.org/privacy/

Search
Search for:
Event host
Equipment Licensing Program (2020)
Close
Search for:
Event host
Equipment Licensing Program (2020)
Privacy
AIBA takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following Privacy Policy carefully to learn more about AIBA’s use of your personal identifying information that AIBA collects when you visit AIBA’s official website at www.aiba.org (hereinafter referred to as: the “Website”). AIBA reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you. You are therefore responsible for regularly reviewing this Privacy Policy.
What this Privacy Policy covers
This Privacy Policy covers AIBA’s treatment of personal identifying information that AIBA collects when you are on the Website and when you use services on the Website, as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy also covers AIBA’s treatment of any personal identifying information that AIBA’s business partners share with AIBA unless otherwise stated.
This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of any companies or legal entities that AIBA does not own or control or to any persons that AIBA does not employ or manage, including without limitation third-party advertisers or sponsors to whom you provide information. AIBA is not responsible for privacy policies or practices of other websites to which you choose to link from the Website, and AIBA encourages you to review the privacy policies of those other websites so you can understand how they collect, use and share information.
Information collection and use
AIBA does not collect personal identifying information when you access the Website homepage and browse the Website without disclosing your personal data except as described in this Privacy Policy or the relevant part of the Website and except cookies (see below under “cookies”).
AIBA collects personal identifying information when you register on the Website, when you use certain products or services on the Website and when you enter promotions, sweepstakes or similar services sponsored by AIBA or its business partners. AIBA may also receive personal identifying information from its business partners.
If registration required, AIBA may request your name, email address, and some other personal information. Once you register with AIBA and/or sign in to our products or services, you are not anonymous to AIBA and the information provided will be held by AIBA.
In the event that registration or sign in occurs via Facebook authentication services (Facebook account), AIBA may receive some information from Facebook, but you remain solely responsible for your whole relationship with Facebook, including, without limitation, any content on the Facebook website.
In case you terminate your membership with Facebook and/or terminate the links between Facebook and our Website, AIBA will delete all data received from Facebook concerning you if you ask AIBA to do so. You can do so using the same easy way as for the ability to access your personal identifying information as defined in this Policy. Further, Facebook may require AIBA to delete data received from Facebook API in case of violation of their terms.
If Facebook will disable any links to our website, AIBA will delete all your data received through the use of the Facebook API, unless it is a basic account information or AIBA have received explicit consent from you to retain your data.
AIBA also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your Internet Protocol address (IP address), which identifies your computer, AIBA’s cookies information and the page you requested.
AIBA uses information collected for three general purposes: for technical administration of the Website, for research and development to achieve and maintain a high service level and for customer information (to customise the content you see, to fulfil your request for certain products and services and to contact you about specials and new products and services).
Information sharing and disclosure
AIBA will not sell or rent your personal identifying information without your consent. AIBA may send personal identifying information about you to third parties when:
AIBA has your consent to share the information;
AIBA needs to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
AIBA needs to send the information to third parties who work on behalf of AIBA to provide a product or service to you (unless otherwise stated so, these third parties do not have any rights to use the personal identifying information AIBA provides to them beyond what is necessary to provide a product or service to you);
AIBA responds to courts or authorities;
AIBA finds that your actions on the Website violate AIBA Website Terms and Conditions of Use or any other AIBA’s guidelines or rules applicable for specific services; or
AIBA finds that it is necessary, as determined in AIBA’s sole discretion, to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, emergency situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any persons, violations to AIBA’s terms of use or as otherwise required by law.
Cookies
AIBA may set and access AIBA’s cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website’s computer and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to help give  you the best possible browsing experience. By continuing to use the Website you are accepting our use of cookies.
AIBA uses its own cookies for number of purposes, mainly to:
access your information when you “sign in”, so that we can provide you with customized content;
keep track of preferences you specify while you are using AIBA services;
estimate and report our total audience size and traffic;
conduct research and development to improve the Website contents and services and achieve and maintain a high service level.
AIBA may allow third parties that are presenting promotions or researching users response to advertisement on some of our pages to set and access their own cookies on your computer. Third parties’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not this one.
Security
If you communicate with AIBA by email, you should note that the secrecy of Internet email is uncertain. By sending sensitive or confidential email messages or information which are not encrypted you accept the risk of such uncertainty and possible lack of confidentiality over the Internet. In certain areas, AIBA uses industry standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.
Generally, AIBA takes precautions to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.
Changes in this Privacy Policy
This policy may be amended from time to time. If we amend the Privacy Policy in any way we will place an updated version on this page of the Website. Regularly reviewing this page ensures that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Website.
Updating your information
You may review, correct, update or change your personal information at any time by accessing your account on www.aiba.org
Privacy compliance
AIBA is subject to Swiss data protection laws when collecting and processing personal identifying information.
Questions or suggestions
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, please send an email to communication@aiba.org
Featured News
AIBA
AIBA Election Committee appointed scrutineers for the Presidental elections
December 10, 2020
One person from each of the Continental Confederations was selected by the AIBA Election Committee to serve as scrutineer on …
AIBA
Domingo Solano withdrew his candidacy for the AIBA Presidential elections
December 10, 2020
The AIBA Election Committee received a letter from Mr. Domingo Solano who informed that he withdrew his candidacy for the …
AIBA
AIBA publishes Confederations reports
December 9, 2020
Presidents of the AIBA Confederations prepared reports for AIBA Congress which will be held on December 12-13, 2020.
The reports …
AIBA
AIBA 2020 virtual Congress schedule
December 3, 2020
AIBA Congress takes place on December 12th-13th and starts at 12:00 CET on a virtual platform.
On Monday, December 7th AIBA …
AIBA
AIBA’s Ethics Chief says election will be fair and democratic
November 27, 2020
The presidential election of the International Boxing Association (AIBA) will be fair and democratic, according to the head of AIBA’s …
AIBA
The consultation process relating to AIBA new Constitution draft continues on the occasion of webinars with Q&A sessions
November 25, 2020
The draft of the AIBA Constitution was presented to the National Federations during series of webinars for each of the …
AIBA
AIBA Election Committee approved seven candidates for AIBA Presidency
November 12, 2020
All seven candidates for the position of the AIBA President were approved by the AIBA Election Committee on November 12th.
The …
AIBA
AIBA announces the list of eligible NFs for the Congress
November 4, 2020
In total, 151 out of 200 National Federations are eligible for the upcoming AIBA Ordinary Congress held on December 12-13, …
AIBA
AIBA’s Interim Chief Pushes Reforms, Calls for IOC’s Support
October 13, 2020
The International Boxing Association (AIBA) is delivering real change through its reform process, according to Interim President Dr. Mohamed Moustahsane. …
Next
Previous
Social
Twitter
Facebook
Follow @AIBA
Latest Tweets
Check it out: such an angle!
Lomachenko vs Valentino, WSB 2013 pic.twitter.com/IV91KCfuOvOctober 1, 2020 8:05 pmAIBA Ordinary Congress 2020 to be held in December virtually
www.aiba.org/blog/aiba-ordinar… pic.twitter.com/lVjHef4Ob9September 30, 2020 7:30 pmAIBA Family congratulate Interim President Mohamed Moustahsane on his birthday pic.twitter.com/1lksZJ9c26September 1, 2020 11:08 amWorld Boxing Association @WBABoxing officially recognized the International Boxing Day on July 22nd
@GilberticoWBA… twitter.com/i/web/status/12862…July 23, 2020 8:02 amBest moments of 2019 World Championships in AIBA International Boxing Day video. Enjoy! pic.twitter.com/mmm7BXd3pWJuly 22, 2020 11:33 am
International boxing events
AIBA World Boxing Championship
AIBA Women’s World Boxing Championships
Olympic Games history
Youth Olympic Games
AIBA Youth World Boxing Championships
AIBA Women’s Youth/Junior World Boxing Championships
AIBA Junior World Boxing Championships
Equipment Licensing Program (2020)
Website bySkylabAIBA International Boxing Association"
